✓ Test 1/46 — Cart: Show order summary
✓ Test 2/46 — Cart: Browse Products link (empty cart)
✓ Test 3/46 — Cart: Proceed to Checkout button
✓ Test 4/46 — Cart: Add product & see in cart
✓ Test 5/46 — Cart: Empty cart state
✓ Test 6/46 — Checkout: Payment step after address
✓ Test 7/46 — Checkout: Fill address & proceed
✓ Test 8/46 — Checkout: Edit saved address
✓ Test 9/46 — Checkout: Cart to address step
✓ Test 10/46 — CMS: Delete page & verify removal
✓ Test 11/46 — CMS: Page renders on frontend
✓ Test 12/46 — CMS: Page appears in admin panel
✓ Test 13/46 — Payment: Handle network errors
✓ Test 14/46 — Payment: Donation amount options
✓ Test 15/46 — Payment: All subscription tiers
✓ Test 16/46 — Payment: Load donation page
✓ Test 17/46 — Payment: Subscription page with plans
✓ Test 18/46 — Razorpay: Mock successful payment
✓ Test 19/46 — Razorpay: Product in cart after add
✓ Test 20/46 — Razorpay: Checkout flow to payment
✓ Test 21/46 — Subscription: Mock successful payment
✓ Test 22/46 — Subscription: Plans in Hindi locale
✓ Test 23/46 — Subscription: Initiate paid plan
✓ Test 24/46 — Subscription: Activate free plan
✓ Test 25/46 — Subscription: Display all plans
✓ Test 26/46 — Subscription: Plan details & features
✓ Test 27/46 — Products: Cards with price & title
✓ Test 28/46 — Products: Hindi locale rendering
✓ Test 29/46 — Products: Navigate to product detail
✓ Test 30/46 — Products: Display products page
✓ Test 31/46 — Category: Spiritual Retreats (Hindi)
✓ Test 32/46 — Category: Satsang Events
✓ Test 33/46 — Category: Spiritual Retreats
✓ Test 34/46 — Category: Astrology (Hindi)
✓ Test 35/46 — Category: Meditation Courses
✓ Test 36/46 — Category: Satsang Events (Hindi)
✓ Test 37/46 — Category: Navigate to detail page
✓ Test 38/46 — Category: Sanskrit & Vedanta Classes
✓ Test 39/46 — Category: Astrology Consultation
✓ Test 40/46 — Category: Sanskrit & Vedanta (Hindi)
✓ Test 41/46 — Category: Meditation Courses (Hindi)
✓ Test 42/46 — Detail: Product details correctly
✓ Test 43/46 — Detail: Add product to cart
✓ Test 44/46 — Detail: Add to Cart button visible
✓ Test 45/46 — Detail: 404 for non-existent product
✓ Test 46/46 — Detail: Discounted price display